(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-19T12:39:34.636867",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
おまるポルカです、おねがいしまーす
I'm Omaru Polka, nice to meet you!
こんばんは、ホロライブの白上フブキです、よろしくお願いします。
Good evening, I'm Shirakami Fubuki from Hololive, nice to meet you!
さて今夜も始まりましたミュージックガーデンでございますけども。
Now, tonight has also begun, "Music Garden".
いやね、私もちょっとね。
Well, me too, a little bit.
髪切った？
Did you cut your hair?
髪はまだ切ってないですけども。
I haven't cut my hair yet, though.
熱くなってきてますのでね、ちょっとばっさり行きたいなとは思ってるんですけども。
It's getting hot, so I want to chop it off.
そうなんですよ。
That's right.
髪切りましたよね、そういえば。
You cut your hair, come to think of it.
いや切ってないよ！
No, I didn't cut it!
切りましたよね？
You cut it, didn't you?
いや切ってないよ！結構前にあの、一緒...
No, I didn't cut it! Quite a while ago...
いや今日はなんか...
Well, today somehow...
あ、はい。
Ah, yes.
ルイくん誕生日。
Lui-kun's birthday.
そうですね、お誕生日ということで、おめでとうございます。
That's right, it's her birthday, so congratulations.
髪切った？
Did you cut your hair?
髪は切ってないですけども、逆に切られましたよね？ショートにね。
I haven't cut my hair, but you had yours cut into a short style, right?
まずは本日のゲストのご紹介です。はい。
First, let's introduce today's guests. Yes.
今夜も豪華ゲストでお送りするミュージックガーデン、
Tonight as well, "Music Garden" brought to you with a gorgeous guest lineup.
なんと今夜は話題の海外グループも中継で繋がってるそうですよ！
Tonight, amazingly, popular overseas groups are connected via relay!
最後まで見逃せません！
You can't miss it until the end!
はい、もうこれ鷹ルイくん...、すっかり常連だね。
Yes, well this Takane Lui-kun... you're quite the regular.
あ、ありがとうございます。今日、ちょっと1回目だと思うんですけど、ありがとうございます。
Ah, thank you very much. Today, I think it's the first time, but thank you.
今日、えっと、としこ...、おれ、白上くん61...
Today, um, Toshiko... I, Shirakami-kun 61...
そうですね、本日で61回目に、ルイとかけてですかね、ありがとうございます。
That's right, today is the 61st time, playing on "Lui", thank you.
ルイよ！61回やってたんだ、この番組。
Lui! You've done it 61 times, this program.
あー、なんか、すいません、なんか私、字が出てしまいましたが、本当すいません。
Ah, somehow, sorry, I let the character out, really sorry.
あ、61回出演してるもんね、君は。
Ah, you've appeared 61 times, haven't you?
61回も出演してました。じゃあ、これからもね、62回、63回と毎回お願いします。
I've appeared 61 times. Please keep having me for 62 and 63.
そうですね。
That's right.
はい。
Yes.
はい、じゃあ。
Yes, well then.
それでは、今夜もよろしくお願いします。
With that, please look forward to tonight as well.
よろしくお願いします！
We're counting on you!
それではミュージックガーデン、スタートです！
And now, Music Garden starts!
最初のゲストは鷹嶺ルイでーす。
Our first guest is Takane Lui.
よろしくお願いします。
Thanks for having me.
Looking forward to it.
よろしくお願いします。
Thanks for having me.
誕生日。
Birthday.
はい、ありがたいことに誕生日なんですよ。ありがとうございます！
Yes, amazingly it's my birthday. Thank you so much!
おめでとう！おめでとう！
Happy birthday! Congrats!
えー！
Whoa!
これ、最近の、もらった情報だと、悪夢を見て起きちゃうんだって？
So, according to some recent info, you've been having nightmares?
そうなんですよ。悪夢めっちゃ見てて、例えばこう、エムガーデンの収録とかで、もう誰もいないとか。
Yeah, I've been having tons of nightmares, like recording for M-Garden and nobody's there.
誰もいない。あとライブ幕が上がったら誰もいないとか。
Nobody's there. Or when the curtain goes up for a live, nobody's there.
そういう悪夢を見て、起きて、泣くっていう、泣いてマネージャーに連絡するっていう、そういう感じですかね、最近は。
Having nightmares like that, waking up crying, and calling my manager... That's how it's been.
マネージャーさん、それ大変じゃないの？
Manager-san, isn't that tough on you?
あの、起きてからね、連絡くれる、おう、よしよしって連絡くれます。
Well, after I wake up, they message me saying, "There, there," and things like that.
マネージャーさんは、君のお母さんか何か？
Manager-san, are you her mother or something?
え、ポルカさんは悪夢とか見ますか？
Um, Polka-san, do you ever see nightmares?
最近見ないな。
I don't lately.
見ない。トワ様夢見るんですか？
You don't? Do you dream, Towa-sama?
夢？覚えてないことが多い、シラカミくん。
Dreams? I often don't remember them, Shirakami-kun.
はい。
Yes.
うん、夢見る？
Um, do you dream?
あ、夢はもうもちろん見ます。
Ah, I definitely dream.
ああ。
I see.
どんな夢？そうですね、最近見た夢は、あの、なんか山の中にいて、
What kind of dream? Well, the dream I saw recently, um, I was deep in the mountains,
山？山。なんかよくわからないキノコを撮ってるという。
Mountains? Mountains. Gathering some unknown mushrooms.
シラカミくんもよくわかんないね。
Shirakami-kun doesn't get it either.
すみません、よくわからない。夢占い行きましょう。
Sorry, I don't get it. Let's go to dream interpretation.
夢占い行きましょう。ね、ご一緒でいただければと思います。
Let's do dream fortune-telling together, if you'd like.
じゃあまた後に行って、調査しましょう。
Then let's go check it out later.
はい、それではそんなです。鷹嶺ルイさんには、高評価のカバー曲「ラブカ？」を披露していただきます！
Takane Lui will now perform her highly acclaimed cover of "Rabuka?"!
よろしくお願いします。
Looking forward to it.
夢覚えていらっしゃらないですか？
Do you not remember your dreams?
ああ、でも熟睡してるんじゃないのかな、じゃあ。
Ah, maybe she's just sleeping soundly then.
はい。それではあの、ポルカさんは「ラブカ？」ご存じですか？
Right. Now, Polka-san, do you know "Rabuka?"?
流行ったやつだよね。
It's that popular song, right?
若い人の間で流行ってて。
It became popular among young people.
ポルさん、おいくつ？
Pol-san, how old are you?
まあ、ウィキペディアとかで見て。
Well, checking Wikipedia and stuff.
ウィキペディアに載ってらっしゃるんですね。
It's listed on Wikipedia?
載ってる、載ってる。なるほど、そうなんですね。
It is, it is. I see, is that so.
長いからね、もう、これもお。今回で何回目夢でしたっけ？
It's long, you know. How many times was this dream this time?
後でマネージャーさんに確認、マネージャーさんに確認して行きましょう。
Let's check with the manager later.
はい、では準備ができましたら行きましょう。それではまいりましょう、鷹嶺ルイで「ラブカ？」！
Here is Takane Lui with "Rabuka?"!
暗い 暗い 深海 ベールに包まれるは ラ ラ ラ ラ ラ ラブか ？
Wrapped in a dark, dark deep-sea veil... is it la-la-la-la-la rabuka?
奪い 奪い 叶わぬ願いは 打ち上げられ さ さ さ さっさと去るか ？
Stealing, stealing, unfulfilled wishes are cast away... will you quickly leave?
届け 届け それでも光は 潰え 水面 その遥か ラブカ
Reach, reach, yet the light fades far beyond the water's surface... rabuka.
クライ クライ 未開の想いは 足らぬ 足らぬ 至らぬは ラブか ？
Crying, crying, undeveloped feelings are not enough, not enough, failing... is it love?
ラブカ ラララ ラブカ ラブ なのか ？
Rabuka, la-la-la rabuka... is it love?
甘き ラビュー ラビュー ラビューか ？ それは バグ バグ バグか ？
Sweet rabū, rabū, rabū? Is it a bug, bug, bug?
嘘と嘘で濁ったアイ アイニージュか ？
An eye-in-you clouded with lies and more lies?
腐る愛 愛 愛か ？
Rotten love, love, love?
噛み砕き 泣く か ？ 届かぬ距離で待っていたってしょうがない
Chewing it up and crying? It's no use waiting at a distance that won't reach.
白亜病 ラ ラ ラ ラ ラ ラブか
Leukorrhea, la-la-la-la-la rabuka...
暗い 暗い 深海 ベールに包まれるは ラ ラ ラ ラ ラ ラブか ？
Wrapped in a dark, dark deep-sea veil... is it la-la-la-la-la rabuka?
奪い 夺い 叶わぬ願いは 打ち上げられ さ さ さ さっさと去るか ？
Stealing, stealing, unfulfilled wishes are cast away... will you quickly leave?
届け 届け それでも光は 潰え 水面 その遥か ラブカ
Reach, reach, yet the light fades far beyond the water's surface... rabuka.
クライ クライ 未開の想いは 足らぬ 足らぬ 至らぬは ラブか ？
Crying, crying, undeveloped feelings are not enough, not enough, failing... is it love?
クライ クライ 未開の想いは足らぬ 足らぬ 至らぬはラブか？
Dark, dark... Is unchartered affection not enough? Not enough? Is this rabuka?
ラブカ ラララ ラブカ
Rabuka, lalala, rabuka
ラブ なのか？
Is it love?
甘きラビュー ラビュー ラビューか？
Sweet revue, revue, is it revue?
それはバグ バグ バグか？
Is it a bug, bug, bug?
嘘と嘘で濁ったアイ アイニージュか？
An "I need you" muddied by lies upon lies?
腐る愛 愛 愛か？
Rotting love, love, is it love?
咀嚼 吐き出し泣くか？
Chew, spit it out, and cry?
届かぬ距離で待っていたってしょうがない
There's no use waiting at an unreachable distance.
甘きラビュー ラビュー ラビューか？
Sweet revue, revue, is it revue?
それはバグ バグ バグか？
Is it a bug, bug, bug?
腐るラビュー ラビュー ラビューは 既に地に落ち絶えた
The rotting revue, revue, revue has already fallen to the ground and perished.
届く距離で出会って嫌になるならやめな
If meeting at a reachable distance makes you hate it, then stop.
白亜病 ラララ ラララ ラブカ
Leukorrhea disease, lalala, lalala, rabuka
ラララ ラララ ラブカ
Lalala, lalala, rabuka
はい、続いては犬神ころねでっす。
Next up is Inugami Korone!
よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you!
これ、みんなは、どういうグループなの？
So, what kind of group are you all?
あ、えっとですね、あの、ま、アニマルフレンド的な、ま、みんなでね、ま、耳もついたり動物だったりするんですよ。
Ah, well, you see... like animal friends, we all have animal ears or are animals.
白上さんはちょっとマイク足りなかったのかな？
Did Shirakami-san not have enough mics?
ちょっとマイクね、足りなかったらしくて、自分になかったんですよ。なんでちょっところさんにマイク借りてて...
It seems there weren't enough mics, so I didn't have one. That's why I'm borrowing Korone-san's mic...
目の前全然出てません
It wasn't showing up in front of me at all, really.
これころねさんはしゃべれる？大丈夫？
Can Korone-san speak? Are you okay?
ちょっと逆で、逆でちょっとマイク分け合って...よろしくお願いします。
It's the reverse, we're sharing the mic... nice to meet you.
間でね、ラムちゃんごめんね、ごめんね...
In-between, Ram-chan, sorry, sorry...
すごいね。
That's amazing.
そうですね、やっぱ遠くの画面で見てると、皆さん動物だらけなので、なんかいいですね。
That's right, looking at the distant screen, everyone is full of animals, so it's nice.
犬たか、ししらむ、コンコン、ネコネック。
Inutaka, Shishiram, Konkon, Nekoneko.
あの、ラムの方がいらっしゃるんですね。
Um, there is someone named Ram, right?
一人だけ食材…？
Only one person is food...?
ラムは、なんでラムなんだろうね？
Ram, why is she Ram?
そっちに聞いてるんだよ！ゲスト様は一人で聞いてるんだよ。
I'm asking you over there! The guest is asking alone.
でもうん、よく見たら周りの、おれ、犬？たか？しし？...羊食べますか？
But well, looking closely, the surroundings... me, dog? taka? shishi?... Do you eat sheep?
まあ、おいしいよね。うん、おいしい。おいしいよね。しゃぶしゃぶかな。
Well, it's delicious, right? Delicious, delicious. Shabu-shabu maybe.
ということですね！
That's what it is!
ということで、今宵はそんな、え、おいしそうな皆さんがね、あんな素敵な楽曲を披露していただけるんですよね。
So tonight, those delicious-looking people will showcase such wonderful songs.
はい、おいしそうな皆さんがちょっと気になったんですけれども、画面の前の皆さんも一緒に盛り上がっていただければなと思います。
Yes, I was a bit curious about those delicious-looking people, but I hope everyone in front of the screen can get excited together too.
はい、それではスタンバイお願いします！
Yes, then please stand by!
お願いします！
Please!
ね、我々雑食ですから、意外とみんな行けるのではないのでしょうかね。
You know, we're omnivores, so maybe everyone can actually eat it.
一番あのなかでやっぱりキャスト的な、食べられる的なのだと、羊？
Among them, as for cast-like, edible-like things, sheep?
まあ、そうですね、やっぱラムが美味しいかと思うんですけども。ラムしゃぶ？ラムしゃぶ美味しいですね。
Well, that's right, I think lamb is delicious. Lamb shabu? Lamb shabu is delicious.
あー、美味しいだろうね、さすがに。
Ah, it must be delicious, as expected.
ね、いいですね。この後じゃあちょっと食べに行きますか？
Right, that's nice. Shall we go eat some after this?
あ、いいね！いるし。あ、いますね。はい。
Oh, nice! There is. There is. Yes.
それでは参りましょう！犬たかししらむで、ウィーク！どうぞ！
Then let's go! Inutaka Shishiram, "weeeek"! Go ahead!
明日っからまた日、月、火 ほら水、木回って金、土、日曜
Starting tomorrow, another day—Monday, Tuesday, look, Wednesday, Thursday, spinning to Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
夢の日々を大事にいきましょう もういっちょ！
Let's cherish our dream-filled days, once more!
明日っからまた日、月、火 ほら水、木回って金、土、日曜
Starting tomorrow, another day—Monday, Tuesday, look, Wednesday, Thursday, spinning to Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
僕ら日々を楽しみで生きてこう さあ行くぞ！
Let's live our days enjoying them, now let's go!
月曜始まったいつもの日々 思い焦がれた週末遠い
Monday started the usual days, the weekend we longed for is far away.
火曜、水曜慣れてきたご様子 作った笑顔引きつったかも！？
Tuesday, Wednesday, getting used to it maybe? The smile we made might have twitched!?
気が付け木曜相当重要 明日の夜からの予定は未定だから金曜一日考えよう
Before you know it, Thursday is super important. Since plans from tomorrow night are undecided, let's think about Friday all day.
自由で壁をぶち壊し行こう
Let's break down walls with freedom!
日々生き抜いて 心は曇り
Surviving day by day, our hearts are cloudy.
僕たちは 過ぎ去っていく
We are passing by.
歩む心を諦めたらそこで負けだ お気楽に行こう
If you give up the heart to walk, that's where you lose. Let's take it easy.
明日っからまた日、月、火 ほら水、木回って金、土、日曜
Starting tomorrow, another day—Monday, Tuesday, look, Wednesday, Thursday, spinning to Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
夢の日々を大事にいきましょう もういっちょ！
Let's cherish our dream-filled days, once more!
明日っからまた日、月、火 ほら水、木回って金、土、日曜
Starting tomorrow, another day—Monday, Tuesday, look, Wednesday, Thursday, spinning to Friday, Saturday, Sunday.
僕ら日々を楽しみで生きてこう さあ行くぞ！
Let's live our days enjoying them, now let's go!
もうどうしようもない模様 やる事いっぱいで気持ちは完敗
A pattern of nothing we can do, so much to do and our feelings are completely defeated.
一日4時間睡眠で 日々この体力を注ぎ込んで
Sleeping 4 hours a day, pouring all this physical strength into day after day.
大人になるってどういう事？
What does it mean to become an adult?
外面良くして35歳を過ぎた頃 オレ達どんな顔？
Keeping up appearances past 35, what faces will we have?
かっこいい大人になれてるの？
Can we become cool adults?
日々生き抜いて 心は曇り
Living through each day, our hearts are cloudy,
僕らは過ぎ去ってく
as we pass them by.
ゆっくりでいい 辞めないで
It's okay to take it slow, just don't give up—
いつか水滴 必ず石を穿つ！！！
someday, water droplets will surely pierce through stone!
明日からまた 日、月、火 ほら水、木回って金、土、日曜
Tomorrow starts the cycle: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun.
夢の日々を大事にいきましょう もういっちょ！
Let's cherish our dream-filled days, once more!
明日からまた 日、月、火 ほら水、木回って金、土、日曜
Tomorrow starts the cycle: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun.
僕ら日々を楽しんで生きてこう さあ行くぞ！
Let's enjoy our daily lives and live on, here we go!
繰り返しの毎日で 行き場のないこの気持ち
In these repetitive days, this emotion with nowhere to go—
めぐりめぐり めまぐるしく回る 毎日を泳ぐんだ
swimming through the dizzying, endlessly spinning days.
めげずにLaugh Laugh (^◇^) もういっちょ！
Don't give up, Laugh Laugh, once more!
明日からまた 日、月、火 ほら水、木回って金、土、日曜
Tomorrow starts the cycle: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun.
夢の日々を大事にいきましょう もういっちょ！
Let's cherish our dream-filled days, once more!
明日からまた 日、月、火 ほら水、木回って金、土、日曜
Tomorrow starts the cycle: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun.
僕ら日々を楽しんで生きてこう もういっちょ！
Let's enjoy our daily lives and live on, once more!
明日からまた 日、月、火 ほら水、木回って金、土、日曜
Tomorrow starts the cycle: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun.
夢の日々を大事にいきましょう もういっちょ！
Let's cherish our dream-filled days, once more!
明日からまた 日、月、火 ほら水、木回って金、土、日曜
Tomorrow starts the cycle: Sun, Mon, Tue, Wed, Thu, Fri, Sat, Sun.
僕ら日々を楽しんで生きてこう
Let's enjoy our daily lives and live on!
ぶっ飛んで眠れ やややや 果たさぬその日まで
Flying high, unable to sleep, until that unfulfilled day—
ご機嫌ななめ よよよよ あなたの周りも よよよよ
grumpy yo-yo-yo, and those around you yo-yo-yo.
息せき切って 服ありありや 約束の日まで さあ掲げよ
Gasping for breath, clothing present and correct, until the promised day, raise it up!
バッテンバッテン ぶっ飛んで眠れ やややや
Cross-cross, flying high, unable to sleep yaya!
向かい風受けて 高く高く飛び立とう
Facing the headwind, let's fly high, high up into the sky.
また雨が降り出しても 私が守るから
Even if the rain starts falling again, I will protect you.
この先に待ってる未来が 分からないけれど 信じている
Though we don't know what future awaits us ahead, I believe in it.
続いてはSSSの3人です。
Next up are the three members of SSS.
よろしくお願いします！
Thanks for having us!
元気。
Full of energy.
元気ですね。
Very energetic.
初登場。
First appearance.
そうですね。
That's right.
ああ、これ気になってたんだけど、
Ah, I was curious about this,
SSSの意味はどういうことかな？
what does SSS stand for?
はい、えーと、頭文字から来てまして、セクシー、センシティブ、戦士です。
Right, um, it comes from the initials: Sexy, Sensitive, Warrior.
センシティブは…戦士は漢字なんだね。
Sensitive is... Warrior is in kanji.
そうそう、そこは分からない。
Yeah, exactly, that part's mysterious.
セクシーが入ってるということは、なんかじゃセクシーなエピソードがあるんでしょうか？
And since "Sexy" is in there, does that mean you have some sexy episodes?
おお、気になる。
Oh, I'm curious.
いや、そうなんですよ。ちょっとね、リッチショコラで、この3人でコラボしたときに、チョコの家でね、ま、この3人じゃれ合いましても、ここには言えないちょこと……
Well, you see, when the three of us collaborated at Rich Chocolat, at Choco's house, we were playing around, but there are things we can't say here—
すみません！
Sorry!
すみませんなんか、ここここちしてまして。
Sorry, we were a bit...
本当に申し訳ございません。ここではちょっと言えない内容になってまして。
We're truly sorry. It's contents we really can't share here.
言えない内容？
Content you can't share?
え、ショコラ？え、えち、えち…ショコラじゃなくて、えちショコラ。
Eh, Chocolat? Eh, Echi... not Chocolat, Echi Chocolat.
なるほどね。
I see.
え、そうするとその、マリーンさんは？マリーンさんもえちショコラ？
Eh, in that case, what about Marine-san? Did Marine-san do Echi Chocolat too?
あ、ちょっと、あの日はえちショコラやらしていただきましたけど、
Ah, well, on that day I did let myself do Echi Chocolat, but
ちょっと言えないようなことをやってたので、
since we were doing things that can't really be said,
詳しくはちょっと、あまりこの番組ではね。
we can't go into details too much on this show.
いや、高校高校に持ってきたね！
Man, you brought it all the way to high school!
そうですね。
That's right.
ま、そんな3人なんですけどね。
Well, those are the three of them.
え、もしかして一緒にやりたいんですか？ いやいや！
Eh, do you want to join us? No, no!
いやいや、私は！
No, no, as for me,
大丈夫ですね。
I'm fine.
ポルさんどうでした？
How about Pol-san?
気になる。
I'm curious.
気に、気になっちゃう。
I'm getting curious.
でもその曲をね、聴いていただいてからちょっとポルさんも決めていただくということで。
But after listening to the song, Pol-san can decide.
今夜はセクシーな楽曲を披露していただけるんですよね？
Tonight you'll be performing a sexy song, right?
そうなんですよ！もう本当にセクシーな私たちにぴったりの楽曲なので、
That's right! It's a song that fits our sexy selves so well,
見ている君たちもメロメロにしちゃいたいと思います！
we hope to mesmerize all of you watching as well!
メロメロに
Completely captivated...
メロメロも自分でする セクシーも自分で言うのもすごい
Saying you're captivated yourself, and calling yourself sexy is amazing.
いやあ、選手か これが 令和の選手。
Man, they're athletes... The athletes of Reiwa.
スタンバイしていただけましょうかね。
Shall we have them stand by?
では お願いします。
Then, please!
はーい、お願いします！お願いしまーす！
Yes, please! Please!
令和の選手な。
The athletes of Reiwa.
令和の選手 いいですね。
Reiwa athletes, nice.
でも令和も まあ悪くないかもね。
But Reiwa might not be bad either.
そうですね。
That's right.
セクシーね。
Sexy, huh.
セクシー、セクシーちょっと感じで いきましょうか。
Let's go with a sexy, sexy kind of vibe.
選手。
Athletes.
では、それではいりましょう。せい、の、せい、の、いふうどうどう！
Well then, let's go. Ready, set, ifudoudou!
[Music]
時には噛んだりして 痛みを覚えさせて
Sometimes bite down, let me feel the pain,
溢れるエキタイで汚してよ 全部
Stain my entirety with that overflowing fluid.
足の先からずっと 蠢かせたその神経はもう
The nerves that wriggled all the way from the tips of my toes,
感触に溺れる 身体ココロを連れて
Take my body and heart, drowning in sensation.
指くわえた我慢の中 欲してんのが理想?
With a finger in my mouth, holding back—is desiring that the ideal?
いらない 全てはいらない 磨き上げる邪気なPRIDE
I don't need it, don't need it at all, a polished, obtrusive pride.
無意味な世界のルールくらい 無駄としか言い様がない
The rules of this meaningless world are nothing if not pointless.
隠しているあなたのSTYLE 剥き出しにあるがままDIVE
Your style hidden away, dive in completely bare.
そこに生まれるのは期待 外れなんかじゃない 頂のSMILE
What is born there is not unexpected—a smile at the peak.
[Music]
吐息を合わせた相性 耳に吹きかける感情
Chemistry with matched breaths, emotions whispered into my ear.
破裂しそうな胸 騒ぎだす細胞
A chest on the verge of bursting, cells beginning to stir.
脱ぎかけてるシャツ 優しく裂いてよ まず かまわず
Tear gently at the shirt coming off, first, without caring.
get フライイングも有り 躊躇わないで darlin'
Get flying is fine too, don't hesitate, darlin'.
自由な世界のど真ん中 夢見てんのが本性?
Right in the middle of a free world, is dreaming your true nature?
いらない 全てはいらない 怯えついた野望のTRY
I don't need it, don't need it at all, a cowering ambition's try.
満足なんてそこにない 目に見える哀れな未来
There is no satisfaction there, a pitiful future in sight.
思い通りにできるLIFE 手にできるかはあなた次第
A life you can make as you please, whether you can get it depends on you.
隠したりなんかしない 誰よりも誇らしげにできるMIND
I won't hide a thing, a mind you can proudly display more than anyone.
ホラこの世界の中 他にはない 確かなもの自分以外は皆無
Look, in this world, there is nothing else certain—none other than yourself.
[Music]
小さくなっている場合じゃない いつだってNo Time! ALL RIGHT
It's no time to be shrinking away, it's always No Time! ALL RIGHT.
上限値超え エンジン全開でいっちゃえ BURN BURN BURN
Exceeding limits, engines full throttle, let's go, BURN BURN BURN.
欲しがってんのはそう 気持ちいいのmore...
What you want, yes, is that good feeling, more...
あるがままの想いでDANCE! イイナリでGET DOWN!
Dance with your raw feelings! Get down as you're told!
いらない 全てはいらない 磨き上げる邪気なPRIDE
I don't need it, don't need it at all, a polished, obtrusive pride.
無意味な世界のルールくらい 無駄としか言い様がない
The rules of this meaningless world are nothing if not pointless.
隠しているあなたのSTYLE 剥き出しにあるがままDIVE
Your style hidden away, dive in completely bare.
そこに生まれるのは期待 外れなんかじゃない 頂のSMILE
What is born there is not unexpected—a smile at the peak.
ホラこの世界で今 解き放て
Look, now in this world, let it loose.
鋭くギラつかせた希望 もっと本気出していいよ
Sharp, glaring hope—you can get even more serious.
[Music]
はい、続いてはオニカンの二人です。
Next up is the Oni-kan duo.
よろしくお願いします！よろしくお願いします！
Nice to meet you! / Please treat us well!
やっぱり仲良いいよね。今日もなんか仲良しエピソードある？
You two really get along well. Do you have any friendly episodes from today?
なんか
Like...
え、ちょっと
Uh, wait...
え、待って、あれ
Wait, hold on...
先ほど、あの、なんかシュークリームを1つ分けてましたね。
Earlier, um, you shared a cream puff, right?
あ、そうなんですよ。
Ah, that's right.
いただきました。
We received one.
皮とクリーム？あ、1つ余ってるのを、あのルイさんがあやめさんにこう、いる？みたいなの
The crust and cream? Ah, Lui-san offered the leftover one to Ayame-san like, "Do you want this?"
いや、中身ぎゅっとあるからさ、どうする？
No, because it was packed with filling, like, what should we do?
1つを丸々、あの二人で半分こして食べたいって言っててね。
You said you wanted to split one whole thing in half and eat it together.
いいの？
Is that okay?
それ、ルイ君は。
With Lui-kun.
まあ、なんか、まあ、甘やかしてもいいかな、みたいな。
Well, like, I figured it's fine to spoil her a bit.
おとなだね！
You're so mature!
こういういい関係性を保ってるコツみたいな感じなの？どうなんですかね。
Is that the secret to maintaining such a close relationship? I wonder how it is.
でも、週にように会ってますね。大体週1で会ってます。
But we meet like every week. About once a week.
ですね、はい。
That's right, yes.
もうすごい。え、そんな会う？
Wow. Wait, you meet that often?
私は ちょっとあまり
As for me, I don't really...
ないですけども、
Not that there is one,
まあやっぱり仲がいいっていうことですよね。
but it means they're really close.
仲がいい証拠ってことだね！
That's proof they get along well!
じゃあもう今日もすごい強調性？
So today, is it extreme cooperation?
調和性？
Harmony?
調和性ね！
Harmony!
ありましたよ、最初ね。
There was some right at the beginning.
調和性なんですか？
Harmony, you say?
はい。
Yes.
じゃあ楽しみだね。
Well, I'm looking forward to it.
それではお二人にスタンバイしていただきましょう、よろしくお願いしまーす！
Now, let's have the two of them stand by. Thank you!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you!
ちょっと調和性だとかえって女幹部が強すぎるかと思いますね。
If it's harmony, the female executive might be too strong.
まあ、鬼と幹部で鬼幹部だからね。
Well, it's an ogre and an executive, so "Onikanbu."
そうですね。
That's true.
調和性であってる？調和性で大丈夫？
Is "harmony" right? Is harmony okay?
調和性だとまたちょっと上下関係がすごいことになっちゃいますので。
If it's harmony, the hierarchy might get a bit intense.
あ、でも鬼と幹部ってさ、実際どっちが上なんだろうね？
By the way, between an ogre and an executive, which is higher?
どうなんですかね、力的にはやはり鬼の方なんですが、
I wonder. In terms of strength, it's probably the ogre,
なんですが、やはりあの、あやめさん少し幼いところがありますので、まだアイスクリームで……アイスクリームでご機嫌だからね。
but Ayame-san is a bit childish, and she's happy with ice cream...
ねえ、まあいい、いい感じなんじゃないでしょうか？まあ、いいと思いますよ。
Well, isn't that a nice vibe? I think it's good.
それでは参りましょう！この二人でね、この曲を聴きたかった方も多いのではないでしょうか？鬼幹部で「チューリングラブ」！
Now then, let's go! "Turing Love" by Onikanbu!
あー、恋の定義がわかんない
Ah, I don't know the definition of love,
まずスキって基準もわかんない
and I don't even know what "like" means as a baseline.
要は、恋してる時が一番らしい
The point is, you look your best when you're in love.
客観？主観？エビデンスプリーズ！
Objective? Subjective? Evidence, please!
愛は計算じゃ解けない
Love can't be solved with calculations,
まず普通の計算も解けない
and I can't even solve basic calculations.
要は、そんな状態が愛らしい
The point is, that kind of state is adorable.
アイノウ？ユーノウ？
I know? You know?
もう大抵の事象において Q があって A を出して解けるのに
Though for most things, you have Q and A to solve it,
勘違って間違って 解けないこの気持ちはなんだろう
misunderstanding and wrong, what is this unresolvable feeling?
DAZING!! モーションは相対性にステイ
DAZING!! Motion stays relative,
チューリングラブ 見つめあったたって解けないメロウ
Turing Love, a mellow feeling that won't resolve even by gazing.
ワットイズラブ いま 123 で証そうか
What is Love? Shall we prove it now with 1, 2, 3?
言葉で生み出すクエスチョン (クエスチョン！)
Questions born from words (Question!)
ハートで高鳴るアンサー (アンサー！)
Answers throbbing in the heart (Answer!)
測ったって不確定性 ぼくらのだから BPM
Measured uncertainty, our BPM.
チューリングラブ 宙に舞っただって信じないけど
Turing Love, I wouldn't believe it even if it danced in the sky,
フォーリンラブ いまは ABC すらバグりそうだ
Falling Love, even ABC seems buggy right now.
なんでか教えてオイラー (オイラー！)
Tell me why, Euler (Euler!)
感想聞かせてフェルマー (フェルマー！)
Let me hear your thoughts, Fermat (Fermat!)
予測不可能性 いま触れてみる
Unpredictability, let's touch it now.
さあ証明しよう (証明しよう) 間違いのないように
Come, let's prove it (Let's prove it) so there are no mistakes.
証明しよう (証明しよう) この感情全部全部
Let's prove it (Let's prove it) all of this emotion.
証明しよう (証明しよう) 正解があるなら 証明しよう (証明しよう) シンプルな Q.E.D.
Let's prove it if there's a correct answer. Q.E.D.
今日こそ証明したい！(したい！) 目に見えない 無理難題を
I want to prove it today! Invisible, impossible challenges.
ASAP! 導き出したい たどり着きたい 最適解へ
ASAP! I want to derive and reach the optimal solution.
何度空回ったってぶつかっちゃったって 不かぎなこのアノマリーを解き明かす過程さえ必要条件です。
Even the process of solving this mysterious anomaly is necessary.
「3次元(立体)における2点 AB 間の距離を求めよ。」的な感じだと思ってたのに
Even though I thought it was like finding the distance between A and B in 3D space,
さあ今日も公式も見当たらないし 参考資料にも載ってないから
formulas aren't found and it's not in reference materials,
君と生み出してみせたいじゃん 3次元(世界)におけるこの気持ちの求め方
I want to create it with you—how to find this feeling in 3D.
丸だってバツだって不安にとってイコールで
Whether circle or cross, equal to anxiety,
近くなって遠くなって揺れるこの気持ちの針も (条件 is 明瞭)
getting closer, farther, the swinging needle of this feeling.
Steppin'!! エモーションは相乗性ミステイク
Steppin'!! Emotion is a synergy mistake.
チューリングラブ 騒ぎ出した胸の痛くなるほど
Turing Love, my chest starts throbbing painfully.
証明はいまも確度を増しているようだ
Proof seems to be increasing in certainty even now.
曖昧も除外して 最大の仮説を いま、ふたりなら実証できそう
Excluding ambiguity, the greatest hypothesis—now, we can verify it.
チューリングラブ 見つめあったたってキリないメロウ
Turing Love, a mellow feeling that won't end by gazing.
ワットイズラブ いま 123 で証そうか
What is Love? Shall we prove it now with 1, 2, 3?
言葉で生み出すクエスチョン (クエスチョン！)
Questions born from words (Question!)
ハートで高鳴るアンサー (アンサー！)
Answers throbbing in the heart (Answer!)
測ったって不確定性 ぼくらのだから BPM
Measured uncertainty, our BPM.
チューリングラブ 宙に舞っただってその因果も
Turing Love, even its causality dancing in the sky,
フォーリンラブ いまは XYZ まで解りそうだ
Falling Love, now we might even understand up to XYZ.
確かめさせてピタゴラス (ピタゴラス！)
Let me verify, Pythagoras (Pythagoras!)
確かにささせてリーマン (リーマン！)
Make it certain, Riemann (Riemann!)
予測済み可変性 いま触れてみる
Predictable variability, let's touch it now.
さあ証明しよう (証明しよう) 間違いのないように
Come, let's prove it (Let's prove it) so there are no mistakes.
証明しよう (証明しよう) この感情全部全部
Let's prove it (Let's prove it) all of this emotion.
証明しよう (証明しよう) 正解があるなら 証明しよう (証明しよう) 推測を超えて！
Let's prove it if there's a correct answer, beyond speculation!
証明しよう (証明しよう) 間違いのないように
Let's prove it (Let's prove it) so there are no mistakes.
証明しよう (証明しよう) この感情全部全部
Let's prove it (Let's prove it) all of this emotion.
証明しよう (証明しよう) 正解があるなら
Let's prove it if there's a correct answer.
証明しよう (証明しよう) シンプルな Q.E.D.
Let's prove it, simple Q.E.D.
続いてはルイスイの二人で！
Up next is the duo of Lui and Sui!
よろしくお願いしまーす！
Please look forward to it!
今日二人で披露してくれる曲は、かなり注目されてると思うんだよね。
The song these two are performing today is getting a lot of attention, I think.
ありがとうございます
Thank you very much.
今日何？聞いてない
What is it today? I haven't heard.
今日は「バグ」を歌わさせていただきます。
Today, we'll be singing "Bug".
あ、バグご存知ですか？バグ
Ah, do you know Bug? Bug?
なん、あの、ば、バグってるやつから
You know, the bugged one, from...
バグってバグって、あの、かっこいいやつだね。
Bugged and bugged, you know, that cool one.
あ、かっこいいやつならもちろんそうそうそう。
Ah, if it's the cool one, of course, yeah.
知ってます。知ってます。
I know it. I know it.
僕は知ってるから。知ってましたけど。
I know it. Well, I knew it.
なんで今回はバグを選んだのでしょうか？
Why did you choose "Bug" this time?
はい、あの、私自身がちょっと歌を頑張りたいって思ったときに、やはりあの、同じ事務所の彗星先輩に、やっぱり歌ではすごく憧れておりまして
Well, when I wanted to work harder on my singing, I really looked up to Suisei-senpai.
で、一緒にもし歌えるんだったら、かっこいい曲を一緒に歌えたらなっていうことで、バグでお誘いさせていただきました。
So I invited her to do "Bug" hoping we could sing a cool song together.
ありがとうございます。
Thank you very much.
ちょっと緊張してる、たかねく。
Takane's a bit nervous.
緊張してます。
I'm nervous.
なんか、さっきまでとはおうちがいというかさ。
It's totally different from until just now, you know.
そうですね。
That's right.
え、じゃあその先輩後輩の彗星さんとの、なんか最近後輩とのあったかいエピソードみたいなのあるの？
Do you have any recent heartwarming episodes with your senior Suisei-san?
は、あっ
Ah...
急ですね。
That's sudden!
あ、そうとかな。
Ah, is that so.
ああ、そうですね。できればね、の、ルイさんとのあったかいエピソードといえば…
Ah, right. Speaking of a heartwarming episode with Lui-san...
あの、このバグのね、お、コーラスがあるんですけども、ほほ撮ってくれました。
Um, for this "Bug" chorus, she almost recorded it for me.
さすが後輩。
As expected of a junior.
そうですね。
That's right.
あの、私が取れずじまいでいたところを、私が取りますというところで、お、撮っていただきまして、
Where I hadn't managed to record it, she said "I'll record it," and recorded it for me—
あ、取りますと。
Ah, "I'll record it."
ありがとうございます、本当になんか、取り、取らせていただいて、取りだけに…
Thank you very much, really letting me record...
まあ、いっ、さ、そう、そうだね。
Well, well, right, right.
じゃあ今日は裏のコーラスも注目だね。
Then today, the backing chorus is also something to look out for.
そうですね。注目、お願いします。
That's right. Please look out for it.
それではサビの方よろしくお願いします。
Well then, please go ahead to the chorus part.
はい、よろしくお願いします。
Yes, please.
よろしくお願いします。
撮りだけで。
Just the recording.
撮りだけにね、そうですね。出ましたね、今回も。出ましたね。
Just recording, yeah. It came out this time too. It did.
なんか、あったかいエピソードというか、なんか、小声のエピソードみたいになっちゃう、ちょっと怖かったけどよかったね。
It's less of a heartwarming episode and more of a whispered one, a bit scary, but it's good.
ね、我々はあったかいエピソードありますかね？
Right, do you guys have any heartwarming episodes?
あー、結構この、今会場と、あの照明あったかいよ。
Ah, quite a bit, like the venue and the lighting are warm right now.
あ、結構そうであたたかいですね。これ61回目ですからね、アビルね。
Ah, quite so, it's warm. Because this is the 61st time, right.
あったかいですね。そうですね、61回目にもなりました。
It's warm. That's right, it's already the 61st time.
じゃあ、行きましょうか、フブキさん。
So then, shall we go, Fubuki-san?
はい、それではまいりましょう。ルイスイで「バグ」。
Yes, then let's go. LuiSui with "Bug".
どうぞ。
Here we go.
迷子 迷子 真っ只中 さあ
Lost, lost, right in the middle, now
パパ パラ パラノイア [ア]
Pa-pa para paranoia, "Ah"
ギコ ギコ MY HEART 剪定
Giko-giko MY HEART pruning
パパ パラ パラノイア [ア]
Pa-pa para paranoia, "Ah"
退路 退路 断った絡まった パパ パラ パラノイア [ア]
Escape route cut off, entangled, pa-pa para paranoia, "Ah"
SAD SAD 突っ伏して叫んだ ぱぱぱ La ぱーらのーい[ド]
SAD SAD prostrating and screaming, pa-pa-pa La-pa-ra-no-i-d
さあ パパ パバグ さあ バグバグ
Now pa-pa bu-bug, now bug-bug
タタ タタグ 才能のタグ
Ta-ta ta-tag, tag of talent
もう ハ ハ ハグ 感情は剥ぐ
Already ha-ha-ha-hug, stripping away emotions
発症「クルシイ」は 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
The onset of "suffering" is no, no, no, no
まあ! 絶叫な感情落下 パッパラノイア [ア]
Well! Screaming emotional drop, pa-para-noia, "Ah"
溺れ声上げては ぐるぐる
Raising a drowning voice, round and round
まあ! 絶体絶命落下 やったら滅多ラ
Well! Desperate drop, randomly and recklessly
沈め ユメユメ 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
Sink, never ever, no, no, no, no
さあ パパ パバグ さあ バグバグ
Now pa-pa bu-bug, now bug-bug
まとハズレズレ 慈愛 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
Misaligned, misplaced affection, no, no, no, no
さあ パパ パバグ さあ バグバグ
Now pa-pa bu-bug, now bug-bug
解答絶え絶え 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
Answers fading, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
狂狂 ぱっかーん 警報待って無理 ぐるぐる
Mad mad pop-bang, alarm waiting, impossible, round and round
せーので回れ (狂 狂 狂)
Spin on the count of three (mad mad mad)
7777 ぱっかーん 警報やっぱ無理 ぐるぐる
7777 pop-bang, alarm, still impossible, round and round
あんのにぐさり (狂 狂 狂)
Piercing deeply (mad mad mad)
エンドレス病み…?
Endless sickness...?
抱っこ 抱っこ いらない子だ
Hold me, hold me, I'm an unwanted child
パパ パラ パラノイア [ア]
Pa-pa para paranoia, "Ah"
いい子 いい子 「頑張れ」の氾濫
Good child, good child, flood of "do your best"
アドミニストレイトー 鳴呼
Administrator, ah
パパ パバグ さあ バグバグ
Now pa-pa bug, now bug-bug
ララ ララグ ランタイム ラグ
La-la la-rag, runtime lag
ロロ ロログ 反抗のログ
Ro-ro ro-rog, log of rebellion
パパ パバグ ぱ ぱ パラぱ
Pa-pa bug, pa-pa pa-ra-pa
パーラノイ[ア] パーラノイ[ア] パーラノイ[ア] 嫌 嫌
Paranoia, paranoia, paranoia, no, no
さあ 絶叫な感情落下 パッパラノイア [ア]
Now, screaming emotional drop, pa-para-noia, "Ah"
左右 行方 も ぐるぐる 悲惨
Left and right whereabouts also round and round, misery
限界狂っちゃって やったら滅多ラ
Reaching my limit and going crazy, randomly and recklessly
ヤミ迷い酔え イナイイナイばあ イナイイナイ×点
Lost in darkness and intoxicated, peek-a-boo, peek-a-boo x dot
絶叫な感情落下 パッパラノイア [ア]
Screaming emotional drop, pa-para-noia, "Ah"
溺れ声上げては ぐるぐる
Raising a drowning voice, round and round
まあ! 絶体絶命落下 やったら滅多ラ
Well! Desperate drop, randomly and recklessly
凍え枯れ果て 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
Frozen and withered away, no, no, no, no
さあ パパ パバグ さあ バグバグ
Now pa-pa bu-bug, now bug-bug
爛れ荒れ荒れ 悲哀 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
Festering, raging, sorrow, no, no, no, no
さあ パパ パバグ さあ バグバグ
Now pa-pa bu-bug, now bug-bug
暗闇マミレ理性 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 今 今 今
Reason covered in darkness, no, no, no, no, now, now, now
嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌 嫌
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
皆さん、まったかねー！
Everyone, matatakane!
鷹嶺ルイ誕生日記念2023グッズの紹介もしていくよー！
I'll be introducing the Takane Lui Birthday 2023 goods!
この後22時から発売だからぜひぜひチェックしてくださいね！
They go on sale at 22:00 tonight, so be sure to check them out!
今回のグッズは4種類のご用意させていただきました！
This time, we have 4 types of goods available!
キャンバスアート、ランダムマグネット、コースター、アイスキューブの4種類となっております！
Canvas art, random magnets, coasters, and ice cubes!
今回のグッズはもちろんフルセット購入特典がございます！
Of course, there is also a full-set purchase bonus this time!
数量限定版には一緒にオムライスを食べる特典ボイス、
The limited edition includes a bonus voice of eating omurice together,
そしてそして私の箔押しメッセージと直筆サイン入りのポストカードがついております！
plus a postcard with my stamped message and handwritten autograph!
数量限定ですがたくさん用意したのでルイ友のみんな、
It's in limited quantity, but I prepared a lot, so I'd be happy if all Ruitomo,
そしてそうじゃない人もお手元にお迎え入れてくれると嬉しいです！
and even those who aren't, could welcome them into your homes!
通常版は直筆サインのところが箔押しサインになっているよ！
In the regular version, the handwritten signature is a stamped signature!
ではでは1つずつグッズを見ていきましょう！まずはキャンバスアート！
Now then, let's look at the goods one by one! First is the canvas art!
グチコ先生描き下ろしのオムライスをあーんしているイラスト！
An illustration by Guchiko-sensei drawn specially of me feeding you omurice!
めちゃくちゃこれ可愛くないですか？しかもおしゃれでしょ！
Isn't this super cute? Plus, it's stylish, right?
色合いもお部屋に馴染むんじゃないかしら！ぜひお部屋に飾って一緒にご飯食べようね！
The color scheme will fit right into your room! Be sure to decorate your room and let's eat together!
続いてはこちら！ランダムマグネット！
Next is this! Random magnets!
トゥーミ先生描き下ろしの可愛い可愛いイラストのマグネット！
Magnets with cute, cute illustrations drawn by Toumi-sensei!
全4種類の中からランダムで1つお届けいたします！
We will deliver one at random from all 4 types!
マグネットといえばやっぱり冷蔵庫に貼りたくなるよね！
When it comes to magnets, you definitely want to stick them on the fridge, right?
4種類全部可愛いからよろしければコンプリートして見てくださいね！
All 4 types are so cute, so please try to complete them if you'd like!
ちなみに私はよだれダラーっとしてるのが特にお気に入り！
By the way, my favorite is the one drooling!
続いてはじゃじゃーん！コースター！
Next is ta-da! Coasters!
飲み物を入れると水滴がついて気になるよね！
When you pour a drink, condensation forms and bothers you, right?
そんな時にこのコースターがおすすめ！
That's when this coaster comes in handy!
金属とコルクの素材なので重厚感があって普段使いでも飾って楽しめるコースターにもなっているよ！
Since it's made of metal and cork, it has a solid feel and can be enjoyed as a decorative coaster for everyday use!
やっぱ冷えた飲み物のグラスをここに置いてプハァってしたいよね！
You definitely want to put your glass of cold drink here and go 'aaah!', right?
ということで冷えた飲み物には氷が必要！最後はアイスキューブの紹介です！
So for cold drinks, you need ice! Finally, an introduction to ice cubes!
私のさまざまなモチーフが入ったアイスキューブ、洗って繰り返し使えるのもアイスキューブのいいところ！
Ice cubes featuring my various motifs, and the best part of ice cubes is that they can be washed and reused!
てかさ、このパネル持ってる人誰なんだろう？
Wait, who on earth is holding this panel?
というわけで、新日本プロレスの試合者
And so, New Japan Pro-Wrestling wrestler
グレート-O-カーンであります！
Great-O-Khan!
おい、この余がせっかく直々にグッズを紹介してやったんだ、
Hey, since I graciously took the time to introduce the goods myself,
ルイ友は必ず完全支配コンプリートを目指せ、買えよ！
Ruitomos, aim for total domination and complete the set—buy them!
おい、それから鷹嶺こんな野郎！
Hey, and Takane, you bastard!
なんだって？プロレスが得意なんだって？しかも…
What was that? You're good at pro wrestling? And...
ああ？誕生日だ？
Huh? It's your birthday?
おいだったらよ、おい！
Hey, if so, hey!
うりゃあ！それ！うおっ！
Take that! Hrah! There! Whoa!
これが余からの誕生日プレゼントじゃ！おい！
This is my birthday present to you! Hey!
ルイ姫、誕生日おめでとう！
Princess Lui, happy birthday!
続いては今週のピックアップアーティストのコーナーです！
Next is the Pickup Artist corner!
今週は海外から今大注目のグループが中継で出演してくれます！
This week, a currently trending group from overseas will appear via live broadcast!
海外アーティスト、楽しみだねこれ！はい、楽しみですね！
An overseas artist, I'm looking forward to this! Yes, I'm looking forward to it!
中継が繋がってる？
Is the broadcast connected?
そうなんです、中継繋がっていますので早速ですが繋いでみましょう！
That's right, it's connected, so let's connect right away!
ホロトリの皆さん！
Everyone in Holotori!
かわいいね！可愛いんですけども…
So cute! It's cute, but...
なんか、さっきまでこっちにいた人もいる？
Wait, were there people over here just a moment ago?
そう、そうですね、いらっしゃいませ。
That's right, welcome.
ああ、早い、早く行った？
Ah, it's fast, did you go quickly?
おい、もしもし、え？
Hey, hello, eh?
さっきまでスタジオにいたいつものルイさんじゃないんですか？
Aren't you the usual Lui-san who was in the studio just a moment ago?
あーなんか、聞こえないな、聞こえづらい、聞こえづらいな。
Ah, somehow, I can't hear, it's hard to hear, hard to hear.
なんかちょっと電波が悪いみたいですね。
It seems like the radio waves are a bit bad.
ああ、でもまだね、まだそういうこともあるんだ。
Ah, but still, there are times like that too.
ということで改めて、ホロトリの皆さんです！
Therefore, once again, everyone in Holotori!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you very much!
あ、ちょっと触れないほうがよさそうですので、ホロトリの紹介にまいりましょう！
Ah, it seems better not to touch on that, so let's move on to introducing Holotori!
ホロトリの皆さんがどんなグループなのかVTRにまとめましたのでご覧いただきましょう！どうぞ！
We've summarized what kind of group Holotori is in a VTR, so please take a look! Here you go!
今週のピックアップアーティスト
[Pickup Artist of the Week]
HOLOTORI
JAPAN, INDONESIA, ENGLISHの国境を越えた
Crossing the borders of Japan, Indonesia, and English,
グローバルアイドルユニット ホロトリ
the global idol unit Holotori.
メンバーは IDから孔雀 パヴォリア・レイネ
Members: From ID, Peacock Pavolia Reine.
ENから不死鳥 小鳥遊キアラ
From EN, Phoenix Takanashi Kiara.
フクロウ 七詩ムメイ
Owl Nanashi Mumei.
JPから鷹 鷹嶺ルイ
From JP, Hawk Takane Lui.
あひる 大空スバル
Duck Oozora Subaru.
5羽の鳥からなる多国語を話せるグループ
A group of 5 birds who can speak multiple languages,
今注目のグループ
a group to watch right now.
5羽の鳥 多国語を話せるグループ HOLOTORI
HOLOTORI, a multilingual group of five birds,
彼女たちの明るさを表現する「にっこり^^調査隊のテーマ」と「セカイ」
features their bright songs, "Nikkori Survey Team Theme" and "Sekai."
この世界、今音楽シーンで欠かせないDECO*27と堀江晶太というホロライブ楽曲も多く手掛けた有名アーティスト2人の夢のコラボ曲。
This dream collaboration features DECO*27 and Shota Horie, prominent artists in the music scene who have composed many Hololive songs.
素晴らしい楽曲とともに、ホロトリが世界へ羽ばたきます。
Accompanied by this wonderful song, Holotori will spread their wings to the world.
いや、いま注目 のホロトリのパフォーマンス、楽しみですね！
Man, I'm really looking forward to Holotori's performance!
うん、これは期待できるんじゃないかな。
Yeah, I think we can really expect a lot from them.
そうですね。ちなみにあの、誰推しとかってありますか？
That's right. By the way, do you have a favorite member?
いや、みんなフレッシュな感じで、すごい可愛かったけどね。
Well, everyone felt so fresh and super cute.
やっぱり箱推し？ は、箱推しっていうんだね。
You support all of them? Oh, that's called "oshi-hako."
そうそうそう。箱推しっていうんですよね、今では。
That's right, supporting all of them is called oshi-hako nowadays.
と、鳥だから？ そういうの巣箱っていう話ではないですね。
Birds? Wait, you don't mean a birdhouse, right?
あ、違う。そうではないですね。では、ではないですけども。
Ah, no. That's not it. Not that.
でも、トリと箱だともうそうなっちゃう。そうなってしまうんですけども。
But "tori" (bird) and "hako" (box) sort of sounds like that...
それはちょっと失礼いたしました。でも、意味はちょっと違うんですけど。
Sorry about that. But the meaning is a bit different.
グループ全部好きなことを最近では箱推しと…
Loving the whole group is recently called supporting all ("oshi-hako")...
みんなも覚えてってね！箱推していこう！ぜひぜひ箱推しをよろしくお願いいたします！
Everyone remember that! Let's support all of them! Please support all of us!
それでは準備ができたようなのでまいりましょう。ホロトリで「にっこり^^調査隊のテーマ」「セカイ」2曲続けてどうぞ！
Well, it looks like we're ready, so let's go! Holotori with two consecutive songs: "Nikkori Survey Team Theme" and "Sekai"!
にっこり調査隊 おこんばんわ
Nikkori Survey Team, good evening!
how are you?
今日も今日とて最高です
Today is another wonderful day!
おお~わんだほーい！
Ohh, wonderful!
探求！ コレクション！ 探求！ E・G・A・O
Exploration! Collection! Exploration! S-M-I-L-E!
諸君！
Everyone!
はい！ 我々は世界の笑顔を調査する！
Yes! We investigate the smiles of the world!
はい隊長 俺に名案がってまだなにもいってないんだが？
Yes, Captain, I have a great idea—you haven't said anything yet?
もー とーにかく あれだほら カナブンは一見にしかず？
Come on, anyway, you know, a beetle is worth a thousand words?
あぁ 百聞は一見にしかずだね
Ah, seeing is believing!
それそれ！
Exactly!
つまり虫取り？ 違うって隊長！
You mean catching bugs? No, Captain!
なになに~？ 提案があります ぜひ聞かせてほしいものだな とりあえず
What is it? I have a proposal. I'd love to hear it. Anyway...
とりあえず 出発しよう ノープランで
Let's set off with no plan!
うん ちょっと待って 出発進行！
Wait a minute! Full speed ahead!
ちょっと待ってって旅支度くらいさせろ~！
Wait, at least let us pack for the trip!
数 日 後
A few days later...
じゃあ持ち物チェックをはじめ~す まずは基本の！
Now, let's start checking our belongings. First, the basics!
ぱ！ぱぱ パスポート持った？
Pa, pa-passport, did you bring it?
はーい！
Yes!
き！きき 着替えわすれた！
Ki, ki-changed clothes, I forgot!
も！モバイルバッテリー持った？
Mo, mobile battery, did you bring it?
はーい！
Yes!
こ！志はもった？ もちろん！
Co, courage/ambition? Of course!
仲間がいて 私がいて しかもフツーじゃない
With friends, with me, and it's not ordinary.
だれのことかな？
Who could that be?
ぼくには不可能を可能に変える何かがあるさ
We have something that turns the impossible into possible!
にっこにっこにっこにっこりコリアンダー
Nikkori-nikkori-nikkori-nikkori coriander!
あちらもこちらも 千客万来！
Here and there, bustling with customers!
君の笑顔もコレクションさせて いいえーい いえいえい いえ~い
Let us collect your smiles too! Yeah!
大人も子供も関係ねえぜ これぞ一流の エンタ~テイメ~ン↑
Adults and kids alike, this is first-class entertainment!
わたしだって いつか 夢を叶えてやるって(we can do it)
Someday I'll make my dreams come true too!
このにっこりに触れて もっと胸膨らみましたとさ good!
Touching this smile made my chest swell even more, good!
そのショッボリをにっこりに変換 うちに任せろ make your smile(Fu~)
Converting that glumness into a smile, leave it to us!
アゲのときだって サゲのときだって かき混ぜちゃって スパイスだって 完ペキだ
Whether high or low, mixing it all up with spice, it's perfect!
なにが？
What is?
にっこにっこにっこにっこりお利口ちゃん
Nikkori-nikkori-nikkori-nikkori good little kids!
大人も子供も 熱烈歓迎！
Adults and children alike, a warm welcome!
もち我々も調査対象だ！
Of course, we are also subjects of investigation!
Run away うぇい うぇい うぇい~い わたしだって いつか 夢を叶えてやるって(we can do it)
Run away, yeah! Someday I'll make my dreams come true!
このにっこりに触れて もっと胸膨らみましたとさ
Touching this smile made my chest swell even more.
ずっと探してたんだよ 特別だって言える場所
I've always been searching for a place I can call special.
なんで僕を選んだの 笑うキミが手を引いたんだ
Why did you choose me? You took my hand with a smile.
だってキミはすごいから 負けらんないなって思うんだよ
Because you're so amazing, I feel like I can't lose to you.
どんな時も僕の中に キミの声が鳴り響いていた
No matter when, your voice was echoing inside me.
怖いんだ なにもない僕だけどできるかな 自信のなさとかしょうもなさでいい勝負さ
I'm scared, I'm just a nobody, can I really do it? My lack of confidence and worthless traits make an even match.
けどキミは「それがどうしたの？」って顔をして 歌を歌うじゃない
But you make a face like "So what?" and sing a song—
それはズルいじゃない？
isn't that unfair?
飛び込んでいこう 僕らのセカイへ 正解の想いに出会えるかな 歌っていたい 踊っていたい
Let's dive into our world, I wonder if we'll find true feelings. I want to keep singing, keep dancing,
痛いぐらい笑えるように
so I can laugh until it hurts.
名前もない 僕らの世界を 迷っていけるよ キミとだから 変わっていこう 願うように
We can wander through our unnamed world because I'm with you. Let's change, as we wish.
今僕ら 期待の未体験を キミの未来を僕が歌うよ 描いてもっと Yeah
Now we step into an anticipated unknown experience. I'll sing your future, let's imagine it more, yeah.
キミの未来を僕が歌うよ
I'll sing your future,
描いてもっと Yeah
let's imagine it more, Yeah.
泣いてもいいじゃん
It's okay to cry,
それも答えだ
that's also an answer,
どうしたっていいよ
it's fine however it goes.
想いは全部零さぬように抱き締めながら
Holding you close so none of these feelings spill out,
キミと見たいセカイへ
to the world I want to see with you.
ホロ鳥の皆さん ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much, Holotori members!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you very much!
これからの活躍に注目していきたいですよねー！
We're definitely going to keep an eye on their future success!
ああ そうだね これは
Ah, yeah, that's right...
ねえ そしてなんと ミュージックガオンでも残すところ2曲になってしまいましたー！
Right! And what's more, there are only two songs left on Music Gaon!
えっ 2曲になったの！？
Eh?! Down to two songs?!
そうなんです 佐藤さん
That's right, Sato-san.
1時間ぐらいの気がしたんだけど
It felt like about an hour though.
1時間ぐらいの番組です こちらね
It's about a one-hour show, this is.
あっという間だったねー
That went by in a flash!
あの 時間調整完璧でございます！
That time adjustment was perfection!
なんとですね この後の2曲は 先ほどホロ鳥の皆さんが披露してくださった
And you see, the next two songs are the ones Holotori performed earlier...
あの セカイを… セカイという楽曲を作りました
that "Sekai"... wait, they created the song called "Sekai".
「セカイ」を作ったわけじゃなくて！
Not that they created the world itself!
「セカイ」っていう楽曲を作ったのでね。そうそうそう、先ほどの楽曲は「セカイ」という楽曲ですね。
They made a song called "Sekai". Right, the previous song was called "Sekai".
それを作った、あの、DECO*27さんと、もう一曲が、博衣こよりさんが書き下ろした新曲！とのことでなんです。
And the other song is a brand-new track written by Hakui Koyori!
新曲の！
A brand-new song!
そうなんです！新曲が！新曲が！
That's right! A new song! A new song!
ここで！人に委ねたんだね！
Handing it off to others right here, huh!
そうなんです ありがとうございます！という事でね、どちらも
That's right, thank you very much! So, both of them...
どちらも強いメッセージ性のある楽曲に仕上がってるとのことです。
have turned out to be songs with very strong messages.
2曲も！？
Two songs?!
2曲！ 今日イチのびっくりですね、ポルちゃん。
Two songs! That's the biggest shock of the day, Pol-chan.
ですねー！
Indeed!
それではまいりましょう！DECO*27さん書き下ろし曲「ラビットホール」、博衣こよりさん書き下ろし曲「ファーストクライ」、2曲続けてどうぞ！
Now then, let's go! DECO*27's written song "Rabbit Hole", and Hakui Koyori's written song "First Cry", two songs in a row, here we go!
もういいじゃん ムキになっちゃって
It's fine to get all worked up,
カッコつけて カッコよくない
acting cool when you're not—
そういうのいやになってんだ
I'm sick of stuff like that.
ほっといてよ 知りたくない
Just leave me alone, I don't want to know.
もういいじゃん やけになってんの？
Fine, are you at your wits' end?
嫉妬したり じっとできない
Getting jealous, unable to stay still,
聞こえないよう 耳塞いだってたって
even when covering your ears so you can't hear,
言って来るじゃん しんどいなあ
you keep saying things, it's exhausting.
僕は誰も覗かないよ だから僕のことそっとしといて
I'm not peeking at anyone, so just leave me be.
うざいだけのバカにははいはいはい
Yeah, yeah, yeah, to the annoying idiots,
ウケる またのお越し待ってるね、だとか
"lol, looking forward to your next visit," and such.
本当は怯えてる 吠えるだけの弱虫
Actually, I'm just a coward who only barks out of fear.
痛いくせに耐えてはいはいはい
Enduring even though it hurts, yeah, yeah, yeah,
いつも平気なフリばっかなの
always putting on a brave face.
僕は壁を張ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないで
I smile while keeping my walls up, don't get any closer.
怖いじゃん
It's scary, you know.
ばかばっか ばかばっか ばかばっか やだ ばかばっか
Idiots, idiots, idiots, no, idiots!
もういいじゃん まだ怒ってんの？
Fine, are you still mad?
ほっといてよ ホッとなできない
Just leave me alone, I can't relax.
見ないように目を逸らしたって
Even when looking away so I don't see,
付いてくるじゃん やっぱり
you still follow me after all.
転がったら起きればいいじゃん
If you fall down, just get back up.
失ったら探せばいいじゃん
If you lose something, just look for it.
いやいやいやいやいやいやいや それでよくない？
No no no no no, isn't that fine?
間違ったら直せばいいじゃん
If you make a mistake, just fix it.
やんなったらやめればいいじゃん
If you're sick of it, just quit.
いやいやいやいやいやいやいや それでよくない？
No no no no no, isn't that fine?
僕は誰も覗かないよ だから僕のことそっとしといて
I'm not peeking at anyone, so just leave me be.
やなこと全部大丈夫だと言えたらいいのにな 思えたらいいのにな
I wish I could say everything bad is alright, I wish I could feel that way.
違うよ デタラメな大正解
No, it's a completely made-up grand correct answer.
いつも僕は損なロールなの
I'm always playing the losing role.
また言いたいことを殺すから もう忘れてくれ
I kill what I want to say again, so just forget about it.
うざいだけのバカにははいはいはい
Yeah, yeah, yeah, to the annoying idiots,
ウケる またのお越し待ってるね、だとか
"lol, looking forward to your next visit," and such.
本当は怯えてる 吠えるだけの弱虫
Actually, I'm just a coward who only barks out of fear.
痛いくせに耐えてはいはいはい
Enduring even though it hurts, yeah, yeah, yeah,
いつも平気なフリばっかなの
always putting on a brave face.
僕は壁を張ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないで
I smile while keeping my walls up, don't get closer.
どうか Ah- Ah-
Please, Ah- Ah-
ほんとばかばっか いい加減ばかばっか
Really, total idiots, half-assed idiots.
とんだバグばっか だせーなって
Flying bugs everywhere, how pathetic,
そんなことばっか 思う僕もやっぱ どうしようもないんだ 罰点超過
thinking like that, I'm hopeless too.
痛いこととか耐えてらんないない
Can't stand things that hurt.
死ねるって僕も口ばっかだね
I'm all talk about dying too.
今日も壁を張ったまま笑う それ以上近づかないで
Today too, I smile with my walls up, don't get closer.
怖いじゃん
It's scary, you know.
ばかばっか ほら ばかばっか
Idiots, look, idiots.
誰かに言われなくたって
Even if nobody tells me,
私の方がもっと嫌いだ
I hate myself even more.
うるさいな
So annoying...
想像が視界を塞いで
Imagination blocks my vision,
惨めな理由を書き連ねる
Listing out pathetic reasons.
教室にずっと居残り
Staying behind in the classroom,
窓の向こうに黒い影があって
There was a dark shadow beyond the window,
何も言わずにこっちを見ていた
Staring right at me without a word.
私は貴方に救われたくて泣くんじゃない
I'm not crying because I want you to save me.
産声は止められないもの
A newborn's cry is something you can't stop.
何千回ともう一度 死に損なおう
Let's botch our death thousands of times over again.
希望と絶望の夜中を纏って
Clad in the midnight of hope and despair,
醜い光を許したいのは
What I want to forgive, that ugly light,
他ならない私だった
Was none other than myself.
息をして 目を開けて
Breathe... Open your eyes...
これが最後かどうか
Whether this is the last time,
知る術はないよ 知りたくもないよ
I have no way of knowing, nor do I want to know.
優しいな
How gentle...
昏々と闇は寄り添って
Darkness nestles closely, deep and dim,
解けない答えを塗り潰した
Painting over unanswerable questions.
窓を挟んで微かに聞こえた
Faintly heard across the window,
それは祈るような啜り泣きだった
It was a prayer-like sob.
私は貴方を救える言葉を知らないけど
I don't know the words to save you, but
寂しいねって声をかけた
I called out, "You must be lonely."
何千回ともう一度 死に損なおう
Let's botch our death thousands of times over again.
希望と絶望の夜中を纏って
Clad in the midnight of hope and despair,
何千回ともう一度 生きる貴方へ
To you, living thousands of times over again,
私も続くよ 窓の向こう側で
I will follow too, on the other side of the window.
醜い光を愛せたとき
When I learned to love that ugly light,
終わらせなかった産声を
That birth cry I couldn't let end,
唄にしよう
Let's turn it into a song.
痛いのとか耐えてはいないない
I'm not enduring any pain or anything—
死ねる
I can just die,
って僕も口ばっかだね今日も
I'm all talk too, aren't I, today as well.
もういいじゃんムキになっちゃって カッコつけて カッコよくまい
Forget it, getting all defensive, trying to look cool...
そんなの嫌になってんだ ほっといてよ 知りたくない
I'm sick of that, just leave me alone, I don't want to know.
楽しくお送りしてきましたミュージックガールあっという間にエンディングの時間になりました
We've brought you Music Girl, and before you know it, it's time for the ending.
やぽるさん今日はどうでしたか
Pol-san, how was today for you?
いや本当にになんか今日も楽しい時間を過ごせたなって感じですね
Honestly, I felt like I spent another really fun time today.
いや1時間ではないような気がしないね
Yeah, it doesn't feel like just an hour, does it?
そうですねなんか2時間くらいなんかやった気もしちゃって
Right? It kind of felt like we did it for around two hours.
そんな言い方したら僕なんか違うんじゃないかな
If you say it like that, isn't it different for me?
そうそうですね。まもしも60分もやってますと、60分に感じる1時間って
That's right. If we're doing 60 minutes, an hour feels like 60 minutes...
え、じゃあこれ振るけど鷹嶺ルイどうだった？今日めちゃくちゃ忙しくなかった？
Ah, then passing this over—Takane Lui, how was it? Weren't you super busy today?
え、何の事ですか？色々分身したけど
Eh, what do you mean? I created various clones, but—
あ、分身？あ、違うんだ。ごめんごめん。
Ah, clones? Ah, that's wrong. Sorry, sorry.
でもね、あの色んなアーティストの皆さんと共演ができてとても嬉しかったです。ありがとうございました。
But you know, I was so happy to be able to co-star with various artists. Thank you very much.
これ、そういえば今日鷹嶺ルイ誕生日？
By the way, is today Takane Lui's birthday?
あ、そうでしたね！ほうとうでも触れましたけども
Ah, that's right! As we touched upon earlier,
おめでとうございます！
Happy birthday!
今更感ありますけど、ありがとうございます！
A bit late for that, but thank you!
なんのよっ て も いい か な
Don't worry about it.
ありが と ね 。
Thank you!
今日 は ね 、 この 後 に メンバー シップ 限定 で
Today, after this, we have...
NG シーン の 公開 配信 と か も
What's "NG"?
NG scene public streams and stuff,
あ 、 あ る 。
Ah, NG?
NG ？
NG?
NG 、 まあ 、 先ほど 私 が 出し まし た けど ね 。
Well, I mentioned it earlier, but...
あはは 。
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
そう いう の を 色々 ちょっと 出し て いこ う か な と 思い ます ん で 、
We're going to put out all sorts of things like that,
メンバー シップ の 方 も 、 はい 。
so for the membership fans...
必見 です ね 。
They're in for a treat, right?
よろしく お 願い し ます 。
Please look forward to it.
ぜひ 遊び に 来 て ください 。
Please come join us.
せっかく です ので 、
Since it's a special occasion,
ゲスト の 皆さん に も 少し 感想 を 聞い て いき ましょ う 。
let's hear some impressions from our guests as well.
まず は 犬神 ころね さん ！
First up is Inugami Korone-san!
いぇーい ！ いぇーい ！
Yay! Yay! Yay!
なんか 近い な 。 だめ 。
Wait, I'm too close! No!
るいるい ！
Luyluyluy!
お誕生日 おめでとう ！
Happy birthday! Congratulations!
ありがとう ござい ます 。
Thank you very much.
犬神 ころね さん 、 いぇい 、 いぇい 、 いぇい 、 いぇい ！
Inugami Korone-san, yay, yay, yay, yay, yay!
また ゲーム し ましょ う ね 。
Let's dance again, okay?
し ま しょ う ！
Let's do it!
いぇーい ！
Yay!
はい 、 ありがとう ござい ます ！
All right, thank you very much!
元気 ！
Genki!
りょ 続いて 、 あやめ さん 、 いかが でし た でしょ う か 。
Up next, Ayame-san, how was it for you?
はい ！ るい ちゃん 、 お誕生日 おめでとう ！
Hai! Lui-chan, happy birthday! Congratulations!
ありがとう 、 ありがとう 、 ありがとう ！
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
一緒 に 歌え て よかっ た よ 。
I'm so glad we got to sing together!
よかっ た よっ て 言っ て くれ て ありがとう ！
Thank you for inviting me!
いぇーい ！
Yay!
また ね ！
See you again!
はい 、 ありがとう ござい まし た ！
All right, thank you very much!
なるほど 、 パタ で カエ でし た ね 。
It was quite a lively stream, wasn't it?
はい 。
Yeah.
かまよ 。
So noisy!
たいへん カエ でし た ね 。
It really was a lively stream.
で は 、 本当に あっ と いう 間 で ござい ます が 、 今夜 の ミュージック ガーデン は ここ まで と なり ます 。 ありがとう ござい まし た ！
Well, the Music Garden stream ends here. Thank you very much!
これ まだ 続く か 、 会う 日 まで 。 さようなら ！
Well then, see you!